[2008-12-09] v1.9.6
Change	: Updated readme.rtf and TLCmd.txt
Added	: Refresh automatically when run dialog is opened.
Added	: Menu icons are part of skin. (context menu icons and sub menu icons.)
Added	: Some nice icons in Office skin by Denny Weinberg.
Change	: Add a separator between folders and files for dynamic items.
Change	: Context menu items reordered.
Change	: Only context menu has side image.
Fixed	: A display problem that could cause blank items (which open sub menus).

[2008-11-22] v1.9.5.1
Change	: About dialog: contact email changed.
Change	: home page moved -> http://sites.google.com/site/chaosplaceorg/tools/traylauncher
	because all google pages sites are blocked in China.
Added	: Office skin (microsoft office 2007 skin) by Denny Weinberg
Added	: German translation "TL_de.lng" by Denny Weinberg
Fixed	: skin and lng names displayed in correct cases now.

[2008-11-20] v1.9.5
Added	: Refresh automatically if command file is changed.
Fixed	: file icon may not be displayed.
Added	: open dynamic directories, using double click.

[2008-10-21] v1.9.4
Change	: Updated readme.
Added	: Run dailog, double-click on the icon will copy command line.
Change	: some change in code.

[2008-07-01] v1.9.3
Fixed	: Run dialog does not search in some cases.
Change	: Limit run dialog input to 512 characters.
Added	: Save settings when shutting down system.

[2008-06-15] v1.9.2
Added	: Run dialog lists available files under entered directory.
Added	: Ignore mid click if clicked multiple times quickly(within 1 second).
Change	: Limit maximum menu width to 384 pixels.
Fixed	: Run dialog command detection and relative path problems.
Change	: Run dialog box displayes the same icon as the menu does.
Added	: New hotkey, ctrl + alt + leftWinKey, popup context menu. (same as alt + rightWinKey)

[2008-06-06] v1.9.1
Added	: Hold "Shift" to ignore global Mid click. 
Fixed	: icon path does not work if quoted.
Change	: Updated TLCmd.txt.  

[2008-05-20] v1.9.0
Added	: Press a key with "Shift" down, to prevent the menuitem form being executed.
Change	: Updated readme and TLCmd.txt.
Fixed	: a bug in TL.dll.
Added 	: a special mode(\\**) to explore My Computer.
Change	: Display menu at last position after refresh.
Added	: Set the file icon.( * mode NOT supported )
Change	: No empty line needed at the end of the command file.

[2008-01-22] v1.8.8
Fixed	: A serious bug that will crash the program in ** mode.

[2008-01-11] v1.8.7
Change	: Updated readme.
Added	: Support multiple wildcards separated by "|" .

[2007-12-24] v1.8.6
Change	: Updated readme.
Fixed	: Crash with empty path environment variable.
Change	: Use new method to tell sub menus from menu items.
Added	: Open run dialog from context menu.
Added	: Mid click open context menu with left mouse button being pressed down.

[2007-11-19] v1.8.5
Added 	: Language selection option.
Added	: Mid mouse click option; to enable this, TL.dll is required.
Change	: Updated language files.
Change	: Show menu at mouse cursor position when TrayLauncher is reopened.
Change	: Check item icon.
Fixed	: Menu gets blank.

[2007-11-12] v1.8.3
Added	: 5 new skins(blue, green, gray, or, red) by Anthony.
Change	: Updated French translation by Anthony.
Fixed	: Skin menu does not work.

[2007-11-09] v1.8.2
Change	: Updated readme.
Fixed	: AutoStart sometimes does not work.
Added	: Run dialog : Alt-Enter to display the file property.
Added	: French translation by Chris
Added	: Run dialog : Drag and drop support and tooltip.
Fixed	: Run dialog : sometimes does not get the correct executable path.
Change	: Some minor changes;
Change	: Updated the default command file "TLCmd.txt".

[2007-09-27] v1.8.1
Change	: Removed the manifest file.
Fixed	: History list not saved in the correct order.

[2007-09-22] v1.8
Change	: Updated readme.
Added   : Menus are now skinable, two simple skins are included by default.
Added	: Run dialog history is saved in TL.ini when quit.
Added	: Run dialog : Search registry for proper executable files.
Fixed:	: Run dialog box do not set the correct working directory.
Added	: TL.ini : Show/hide hidden files and folders for wildcard items.
Change	: Commandline parameters removed.

v1.6.0.370
Added	: A configuration file TL.ini, to save settings, now only 4. 
Change	: Now use right click to close the "About" dialog box.
Fixed	: Run dialog path sometimes contains %1 at the end.

[2007-07-14] v1.6.0.360
Change	: Improved speed.
Change	: In the exit confirm dialog box, the default button is now set to Yes;
Change	: some code improved.
Fixed 	: commandline does not accept "", and other minor fixes.

[2007-06-19] v1.5.0.352
Change	: Run dialog box UI, preview moved to above.
Added	: Run dialog box displays all of the found commands.
Fixed	: Run dialog box preview icons do not match exactly.

[2007-06-09] v1.5.0.350
Change	: Updated readme.
Added	: The tray icon is customizable; so is the run dialog box default icon.
Added	: A Language file "TL.lng"(a unicode text file) to support multilingual user interface.
Added	: A new wildcard mode(*+*) for advanced users.
Added	: Execute dialog, Auto complete known commands, icon and command (or fullpath) preview.
Change	: Program renamed to "TrayLauncher" from "TrayStart"; command file renamed to "TLCmd.txt" from "TSCmd.txt".
Change	: Execute dialog, History list can has 50 items.
Fixed	: Execute dialog, allow long commands.

[2007-05-11] v1.4.0.282
Change	: Optimized some code and speed.
Fixed	: Execute dialog position not correctly remembered.
Fixed	: Execute dialog history list display problem.

[2007-05-09] v1.4.0.249
Added	: A new Hotkey: Shift + LeftWinkey.

[2007-04-29] v1.4.0.232
Added	: Sort menu items added by wildcard.
Added	: A default icon for unknown files.
Change	: Some code has been rewritten.
Fixed	: "**" mode don't work well with heavy folders.

[2007-04-26] v1.3.0.170 (not public release)
Change	: Display "Empty" for an empty folder.
Change	: Optimized dynamic menu.

[2007-04-25] v1.2.0.164
Change  : Relative path now works well.
Change  : Some change in readme.
Change  : A New ** mode example in TSCmd.txt

[2007-04-24] v1.2.0.162
Change  : "**" mode should now work better.

[2007-04-19] v1.1.0.141
Added	: Now the execute dialog supports commands with parameters.
Added	: Support xp themes.

[2007-04-14] v1.1.0.133
Change  : Compressed with UPX
Fixed	: Execute dialog sometimes does not get input focus.

[2007-04-12] traystart v1.0.1.109
Added 	: an execute dialog, it's like the native run dialog. Use hotkey "Ctrl + leftWinkey" to launch it.
Change	: readme.rtf .
Fixed 	: program silently quit problem when press Alt + space.
Removed	: changeable About logo image. It's not very useful.

[2007-02-09] traystart v1.0.1.88
changeable About dialog logo image.
updated readme
some minor fix

[2007-02-04] traystart v1.0
first release.